landmarkcinemas.com 2019-12-30

# Landmark Cinemas Privacy Policy

**Last updated: November 23, 2016**

This Privacy Policy provides you with information regarding the practices of Landmark Cinemas Canada LP with respect to the collection, use, retention, storage and disclosure of your Personal Information by Landmark Cinemas Canada LP (“ **Landmark** ”), Suite 100, 14505 Bannister Rd SE Calgary, Alberta T2X 3J3, **** by the website landmarkcinemas.com.

The following defined terms are used in this Privacy Policy:   
**“We” or “us”** means Landmark Cinemas Canada LP and our Affiliates.  
“ **Site** ” means the Landmark website at [www.landmarkcinemas.com](https://www.landmarkcinemas.com/).  
“ **Personal Information** ” means information about you as an identifiable individual.  This includes information such as your name, home address, telephone number, personal e-mail address, and personal social media addresses.  If you are an individual and not a business organization, your business address, title, and business telephone number are not Personal Information when used for business purposes.  
“ **Affiliates** ” means our affiliates, subsidiaries and other related entities.   
“ **Service Providers** ” means other companies and individuals who provide us with services but who are not our employees or Affiliates.  
We may update this Privacy Policy without prior notice to you, and any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. ****

**QUICK LINKS**  
Click on one of the links below to access the content of the listed section:

  * **Application of this Privacy Policy**
  * **Information we collect**
  * **Children and Minors**
  * **Uses of the information we collect**
  * **How we obtain your consent**
  * **How we share your information**
  * **How we store and protect your Personal Information**
  * **Links to external content**
  * **Cookies, advertising and how to opt-out**
  * **Accessing your Personal Information**
  * **How to contact us**

* * *

**1.Application of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information that we collect through the Site and when you contact us. 

**2.Information we collect**

We collect information when you provide it to us.  We also collect information about you through automated technologies on our Site and from third parties.  When we link information to you that was collected through automated technology, we treat that information as Personal Information.

**Information that you provide**  
Landmark and our Affiliates and Service Providers collect Personal Information from you when you provide it.  For example, you might provide us with your Personal Information when you e-mail us, sign up for an e-mail newsletter, participate in a promotion, survey or other feature of the Site, register for an account, make payment on your account, communicate or interact with us through our Site. ****  
If you do not want your Personal Information collected, please do not submit it. ****

**Automated information and cookies**  
When you visit or interact with us, we and our Affiliates and Service Providers may use technologies that automatically collect information about how you access, navigate and leave our Site.  For example, we will collect information on what other website you came from before visiting the Site, what browser type and operating system you are using, the internet protocol (IP) address you are accessing the Site from, the pages you are navigating through and what website you go to after visiting our Site.  In general, we do not associate this type of information with other Personal Information about you except in the case of an investigation into our website security.

Our Site uses cookies.  Cookies are data files that are placed on the device you use to access our Site.  These cookies may be used to remember your language preference and to facilitate your navigation of our Site.  We may also use technologies such as web beacon technologies (sometimes referred to as pixel tags and clear GIFs).  These are transparent images that provide us, our Affiliates or our Service Providers with information about whether a webpage or e-mail has been viewed or forwarded and may communicate with our servers or those of our Affiliates, or our Service Providers in order to obtain images and other content and to relay information about the IP address being used to access our Site and information about your browser.  We use cookies and web beacons to present advertisements to you that we think may be of interest to you.  Although the information we collect through cookies and web beacons is typically not combined with information that would identify you, there is the potential for this information to be associated with you and, therefore, we treat it as Personal Information.

This Site uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“ **Google** ”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. 

Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this Site.   
Please also see cookies, advertising and how to opt-out for more information on how we use cookies and web beacons and how you may opt-out.

**Information from third parties**  
We may collect or receive information about you from third parties.  If you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from us, we may receive information about you. 

**3.Children and Minors**

The Site is not directed to or suitable for children under 13.  We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under 13 years of age.  If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete this information from our records or, if that is not reasonable, we will take reasonable available steps to de-identify the information.  Children who are over the age of 13 but under the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which they reside should not provide us with Personal Information without their parent’s or guardian’s consent.

**4.Uses of the information we collect**

We use information collected from you for business purposes.  For example, we use Personal Information:

  * to provide you with services and information you have requested from us, including your use of the Site. We may from time to time use your Personal Information to contact you about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to our services;
  * if you indicated that you were interested in receiving offers or information from us or certain of our Affiliates or Service Providers, we may send you email materials and other mailings about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. If at any time you would like to end your subscription to any such email materials, follow the directions posted at the bottom of the email material; 
  * if you enter a contest or other promotion offered on our Site, we may, under the rules of the promotion, use your name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion;
  * to provide legal notices.

In addition, we use information in order to learn about our customers in order to improve our Site and to develop new products and services.  For example, we use information received from automated technologies such as your domain type, IP address and clickstream information to determine how many visitors visit areas of our Site, how long they remain on our Site, and whether they use the hyperlinks we provide.  Please also see Cookies, advertising and how to opt-out for more information on how we use cookies and web beacons and how you may opt-out.

**5.How we obtain your consent**

You consent to the collection, storage and use of your Personal Information when you provide it to us or you provide it to a third party and give the third party permission to send that information to us.  The purposes for the collection of Personal Information that you provide to us are usually stated or implicit in the context in which you gave it to us or a third party acting on our behalf.  If we want to make additional uses of your Personal Information, we will ask you for your express consent.  For example, if you provide us with your e-mail address so that we can provide you with a newsletter, we obtain your implied consent to use your e-mail address for providing you with our newsletters.  If you provide us with your e-mail address when you make an inquiry, we obtain your implied consent to use it for the purposes of responding to your inquiry.  We may ask you for your opt-in consent to use your e-mail for other purposes, such as adding you to our newsletter list.  
We use opt-out consent for cookies and web beacons and other automated information.  If you do not want us to collect or use this information, please do not visit our Site.  In addition, you may opt-out by using browser settings that will not accept cookies or setting your e-mail application to not download images.  In addition, you may opt-out of certain on-line advertising.  Please see Cookies, advertising and how to opt-out for more information.

**6.How we share your information**

We may share information we collect about you in the following circumstances.

**Affiliates and Service Providers providing services to us or on our behalf**  
Our Affiliates and Service Providers provide services to us and may provide services to you on our behalf.  We may share your Personal Information or information that we have collected through automated means on our Site with our Affiliates and Service Providers.  For example, our Affiliates and Service Providers may host our Site, analyze data collected from our Site, provide customer services on our behalf, administer our promotions, provide marketing or promotional assistance, post our advertisements, and collect your feedback on our Site and advertisements.

**Aggregated or de-identified information**  
We may share information in aggregated statistics and de-identified form with third parties, which does not include your Personal Information.

**When you specifically agree to us sharing your information**  
In some situations, you may specifically agree to us sharing your information.  For example, if you provide us with your contact information, e-mail address, Facebook account, or Twitter account for the purposes of signing up for information or marketing offers from an Affiliate, Service Provider or other third party, we may share your Personal Information for that purpose.  Your Personal Information will be subject to the privacy policy and business practices of our Affiliate, Service Provider or other third party.

**Business Mergers or Acquisitions**  
We may sell or purchase our shares or assets, or enter into other transactions.  If another entity acquires us or all or a portion of our assets or we are involved in a corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, information that we collected from you may be shared with that entity.  The information will be shared for the purpose of that entity considering whether to enter into the transaction and also to complete the transaction.  Should such a sale or transfer or other transaction occur, we will use reasonable efforts to cause that entity to use your information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and the purposes for which the information was originally collected.    

**Other legally required or permitted disclosures**  
We may also disclose your Personal Information in the following circumstances: (a) if such disclosure is necessary for us to receive legal advice; (b) to collect a debt from you; (c) if we are required to disclose your Personal Information in order to comply with any legal obligation or the decision of a judicial authority; (d) if disclosure is requested by an investigatory body, law enforcement official or governmental authority which has lawful authority to request the disclosure of the information in respect of an investigation; (e) if we have reasonable grounds to believe that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or contravention of a law; or (f) where we are otherwise permitted to do so by applicable law.

**7.How we store and protect your Personal Information**

We retain your Personal Information to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected.  We maintain and also require our Service Providers to maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your Personal Information.  For example, we use password protection where appropriate and limit access to staff, employees, Affiliates and Service Providers who need to have access to it for the purposes for which it was collected and who have acknowledged their obligations to protect your Personal Information.  When we transfer your Personal Information, we use encryption where appropriate. Please understand, however, that we cannot and do not guarantee the security of your Personal Information.

If you are located in Canada, please be aware that information we collect may be transferred to and processed in the United States and other countries in which our Affiliates and Service Providers have operations, and will be subject to the laws of those jurisdictions, which may be different from Canada’s laws. 

**8.Links to external content **

Our Site may link or direct you to other websites, services or external content resources which are outside of our control.  Once you have left our Site, we cannot safeguard and are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any Personal Information which you provide on other websites.  These other websites may send their own cookies to your device and may independently collect data or solicit Personal Information.  Please review the applicable terms of use and privacy policies for those other websites.

**9.Cookies, advertising and how to opt-out**

We, or our third-party advertising Service Providers, may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies.  We use these technologies to gather statistical information such as your use of our Site, and whether you have opened e-mail advertising from us, and for other marketing purposes, including delivering advertising to you.

If you would prefer not to accept cookies, most browsers will allow you to: (i) change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a cookie, which lets you choose whether or not to accept it; (ii) disable existing cookies; or (iii) set your browser to automatically reject any cookies.  You may also set your e-mail options to prevent the automatic downloading of images that may contain technologies that would allow us to know whether you have accessed our e-mail and performed certain functions with it.

You may also opt-out of network advertising programs that track your activities across multiple websites to deliver personalized advertising content to you.  Please visit [Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada Opt-Out Page](http://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising), [NAI Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and the [Ad Choices Opt-Out Page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).  
These websites provide tools that identify member companies that have cookies on your browser and provides mechanisms to opt-out of those cookies.  You will still receive other types of advertising from participating companies; however, it will not be based on your interests.  Deleting browser cookies can remove your opt-out preferences, so you should use these tools periodically to ensure that your preferences are up-to-date.

**10.Accessing your Personal Information**

If you wish to verify, correct, or update any of your Personal Information collected by us or our Service Providers or Affiliates acting on our behalf and that we have received from these Service Providers or Affiliates, you may do so by contacting us at the address listed below in “How to Contact Us.”

Please note that we may request Personal Information from you in order to authenticate your identity before providing you with access to your Personal Information or complying with any request to correct or update your Personal Information.    
Please also note that in some cases we may legally deny you access to the information that we have collected about you.  For example, this may occur where the information is subject to solicitor-client privilege or consists of references to other persons or proprietary information that cannot be severed from your information.

We may routinely delete certain records that contain Personal Information in accordance with our record-keeping practices.  Although we will make efforts to comply with any request that you may make to destroy Personal Information about you that is not otherwise required by us to fulfill legal requirements or to protect our interests, you should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your Personal Information from our databases without some residual copies of data because of back-ups, archival systems and other reasons.  We will not, however, continue to use your Personal Information for active purposes once you have requested us not to do so.

**11.How to contact us **

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b5c5c7dcc3d4d6ccdad3d3dcd6d0c7f5f9d4dbd1d8d4c7ded6dcdbd0d8d4c69bd6dad8);
  * by telephone at 1-403-262-4255; or
  * by mail at:
    * Attn: Guest Services

Landmark Cinemas   
Suite 100, 14505 Bannister Rd SE  
Calgary, Alberta  
T2X 3J3
